Guide to the Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) Periodicals Collection, 1957-2017 RL.01399
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Addition, 2015-2016
  - Lesbian Connection, v. 28, no. 4; v. 29, no. 4 (Box 100)
  - Women of Power, no. 16, 22 (Box 100)
  - The Women's Movement, no. 63 (Box 100)
  - The Advocate, no. 651 (Box 100)
  - Spare Rib, no. 112, 161, 166, 170-173 (Box 100)
  - Spare Rib, no. 174-183 (Box 101)
  - The Feminist Art News (Box 101)
  - The Lesbian Tide, v. 4, no. 6 (Box 101)
  - Lesbian Tide, v. 9, no. 5 (Box 101)
  - Black Lesbian Newsletter, v. 1, no. 2-6 (Box 101)
  - Woman to Woman, v. 1, no. 7 (Box 101)
  - Media Report to Women, v. 3, no. 3, 5-12; v. 4, no. 1-6, 8-12; v. 5, no. 1-2, 12 (Box 101)
  - Women's Self Defense, v. 1, no. 2 (Box 101)
  - Taste of Latex, v. 1, no. 1-3, 5-7, 10 (Box 102)
  - Meeting Ground, no. 1, 7-8 (Box 102)
  - Amethyst, no. 9-10 (Box 102)
  - Cuir Underground, v. 1, no. 1-2, 4-8; v. 2, no. 1-6; v. 3, no. 3-8; v. 4, no. 2 (Box 102)
  - Off Our Backs, v. 9, no. 2 (Box 102)
- Addition, 2017-2018
  - Sisters, v. 4, no. 4-6 (Box 103)
  - One: The Homosexual Viewpoint, v. 9, nos. 3, 9-12 (Box 103)
  - The Harlot Herald: Western Edition, February, 1985 (Box 103)
  - Plexus: Bay Area Women's Newspaper, v. 7, no. 4, June 1980 (Box 103)
  - On Our Backs, v. 5, nos. 2-3 (Box 103)
  - Resist: A Woman's Place is in the Revolution, 2017 (Box 103)
  - Socialist Women: National Paper of the Socialist Woman Groups, 1972 (Box 103)
  - Majority Report, May 10, 1974 (Box 103)
  - Black Maria: Chicago Women Speak (Box 103)
  - People's Peace Treaty, March 1971 (Box 103)
  - Notes From the Second Year: Women's Liberation, 1970 (Box 103)
  - The Monthly Extract: An Irregular Periodical, March-April 1973 (Box 103)
  - Women Speaking, v. 2, no. 30, April 1972 (Box 103)
  - The Second Wave: a magazine of the new feminism, v. 1, nos. 1-3, 1971 (Box 103)
  - Women of the Whole World: Journal of the Women's International Democratic Federation, 1973 (Box 103)
  - Off Our Backs: a women's liberation bi-weekly, v. 1, nos. 14-15, 18, 21, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Off Our Backs: a women's news journal, v. 3, nos. 5-6, 1973 (Box 104)
  - Shrew (Women's Liberation Workshop), v. 3, nos. 1-3, 5-9 (Box 104)
- Alphabetical List by Title
  - Ache: Box 42
  - The Advocate: Boxes 84, 87, 100
  - Ain't I a Woman?: Box 18
  - Alabama Forum: Box 90
  - Alone Together: Box 42
  - Alternative Media: Box 94
  - Las Amantes de la Luna: Box 42
  - Amazon Quarterly: Boxes 22, 42
  - The American Sunbather: Box 42
  - Amethyst: Box 42, 102
  - Anti-Racism Newsletter: Box 93
  - Anything That Moves: Box 42
  - Aphra: Boxes 20, 85
  - Arena Review: Box 94
  - Art Journal: Box 6
  - Artworkers News: Box 6
  - Astraea: Box 42
  - Astraea Bulletin: Box 76
  - At the Crossroads: Box 91
  - Atalanta: Boxes 12, 42
  - ATF News: Box 94
  - The Atlantic: Box 6
  - Au Courant: Box 13
  - Aurora: Box 42
  - Avanti: Box 42
  - Awakening: A Womyn's Reality: Box 4
  - AWID: Box 80
  - Azalea: Boxes 20, 42
  - Bad Attitude: Box 72
  - The Barb: Box 90
  - Battle Acts: Boxes 6, 42
  - Bay Area Career Women: Box 43
  - Bay Area Feminist Federal Credit Union (BAFFCU) Bulletin: Box 43
  - Bay Area Women's Liberation Newsletter: Box 77
  - Belles Lettres: Box 43
  - Big: Box 43
  - Big Apple Dyke News: Box 43
  - The Big Boys: Box 43
  - Bitch: The Women's Rock Mag with Bite: Box 4
  - Bitch: The Women's Rock Newsletter with Bite: Box 4
  - Black Lesbian Newsletter: Box 101
  - Black Maria: Box 43
  - The Blatant Image: Box 43
  - Body: Box 43
  - The Body Politic: Box 43
  - The Bond: Box 43
  - Bootlegger Magazine: Box 86
  - Boy Friends: Box 43
  - Bridges: Box 19
  - Broomstick: Box 34
  - Brown Sister: Box 13
  - C??A C?OBA
  - Cahiers du Feminisme: Box 44
  - Les Cahiers du Grif: Femmes Entre Elles: Box 44
  - Calyx: Boxes 36, 44, 45, 46, 72
  - Camping Women Trails: Box 97
  - Cassandra: Radical Feminist Nurses Newsjournal: Box 94
  - Carolina Lesbian News: Box 97
  - The Celibate Woman: Box 94
  - Center Happenings: Box 74
  - The Center Voice: Box 75
  - Chalk Circle: Box 5
  - Changing Men: Box 46
  - Charlotte Free Press: Boxes 21, 46
  - Chrysalis: Boxes 22, 46, 85, 97
  - Ciao!: Box 46
  - Circles: Box 84
  - Citoyennes: Box 47
  - Clothed With the Sun: Box 78
  - CLOUTReach: box 97
  - Coalition Quarterly: Box 77
  - Common Lives, Lesbian Lives: Boxes 17, 20, 84, 93
  - Communist: Box 47
  - Community Connections: Box 89
  - Conditions: Box 17
  - Connexions: International Women's Quarterly: Box 95
  - Coq d'Or (The Golden Cock): Box 47
  - Country Women: Boxes 18, 21, 23, 41, 47, 97
  - Cowrie: Box 47
  - Coyote Howls: Box 47
  - Craft Horizons: Box 5
  - Crossroads: Box 86
  - Cuba Resource Center Newsletter: Box 6
  - Cuba Review: Box 13
  - Cuir Underground: Box 102
  - Curve: Box 87
  - Dade Times: Box 94
  - Davka: Box 47
  - Deneuve: Box 47, 82, 83, 84
  - Des Femmes: Box 47
  - Des Femmes Hebdo: Box 48
  - Desire: Box 48
  - Desormais: Box 48
  - Dilettante: Box 49
  - Dimensions: Box 97
  - Dinah: Box 49
  - Discovery: Box 49
  - Do It NOW: Box 81
  - Double-F: Box 49
  - The Down East Voice: Box 97
  - Dragon: Box 76
  - Drum: Box 49
  - Dungeon Master: Box 72
  - Durham YWCA: Box 77
  - Dyke Digest: Box 49
  - Dykes and Gorgons: Box 49
  - Eastern Region Producers Newsletter: Box 76
  - Echoes from the Sanctuary: Box 86
  - Effe: Box 49
  - Elizabeth Stone House Community Update: Box 95
  - Emergency Librarian: Box 86
  - Emma: Boxes 49, 77
  - L'erba Voglio: Box 49
  - Equality News: Box 98
  - Evergreen Chronicles: Box 18
  - Everywoman: Box 40
  - F Magazine: Box 49
  - FAAR and NCN: Box 76
  - Fag Rag Gay Sunshine: Box 77
  - Fair Play: Box 81
  - Feelings: Box 49
  - Fem.: Box 49
  - The Female Experience: Box 77
  - Feminary: Box 84, 92
  - Feminist Art Journal: Boxes 5, 6, 17, 100
  - Feminist Art News: Box 101
  - Feminist Bookstore News: Boxes 8, 50
  - Feminist Connection: Box 20
  - FEMRITE: Box 78
  - Fireweed: Box 72, 93
  - Fizeek Art Quarterly: Box 51
  - Flaming Faggot: Box 23
  - Florida NOW Times: Box 36
  - Focus: Boxes 3, 4, 51
  - Folk Roots: Box 89
  - Forte: Box 94
  - The Fox: Box 5
  - FPS: A Magazine of Young People's Liberation: Box 51
  - The Freedom Socialist: Box 51
  - Friendly Woman: Box 34
  - Frighten the Horses: Box 51
  - From Lammas: The Little Review: Box 51
  - Frontiers: Box 84
  - Front Page: Box 20
  - Fuor!: Box 51
  - The Furies: Box 85
  - Fuse: Box 94
  - Fusion: Box 7
  - The Gay Alternative: Box 52
  - The Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation, Inc.: Box 78
  - Gay Community News: Boxes 21, 52, 84
  - Gay Forum: Box OS 1
  - Gay People's Chronicle: Box 98
  - Gay Sunshine: Box OS 1
  - Girl Jock: Box 52
  - Girlfriends: Boxes 13, 52, 53
  - Girls Like Us: Box 53
  - The GLAAD Bulletin: Box 77
  - Goodbye to All That: Box 41
  - Gossip: Box 92
  - Gotham: Box OS 1
  - Great Guys: Box 53
  - Grecian Guild Pictorial: Box 53
  - Grecian Guild Studio Quarterly: Box 53
  - Green Line: New News for Western North Carolina: Box 94
  - The Greyhuff Review: Box 53
  - Grumin: Box 81
  - Guardian: Box 7
  - Hag Rag: Box 53
  - Hasha: Box 53
  - Hashte Mars: Box 4
  - Health Rights News: Box 41
  - Heavenly Bodies: Box 53
  - Heresies: Boxes 10, 11, 53, 84, 91, 94
  - Histoires d'elles: Box 53
  - The Hot Seat: Box 53
  - Hothead Paisan: Box 93
  - Hot Wire: Boxes 4, 53, 54, 75, 100
  - Hue Points: Box 94
  - Hues: Box 54
  - The Human Factor: Box 80
  - Hurricane Alice: Box 78
  - HX for Her: Box 75
  - HX: Box 76
  - Identity House Journal: Box 87
  - I Know You Know: Box 74
  - IKON: Boxes 20, 54, 72, 73
  - I Know You Know: Box 74
  - International Nudist Sun: Box 54
  - In Your Face: Box 4
  - Issues! The Magazine for Lesbians of Color: Box 54, 77
  - Issues Quarterly: Box 78
  - The James White Review: Box 54
  - Jane and Jane: The Home and Family Magazine: Box 54, 84
  - Jr.: Box 54
  - Jump Cut: Box 84
  - Kanga: Box 81
  - Kanga Special Edition: Box 81
  - The Kansas City Woman: Box 55
  - Kinesis: Box 13
  - Knotty: Box 73
  - Labyrinth: The Philadelphia Women's Newspaper: Box 95
  - The Ladder: Box 55, 99
  - Lady-Unique-Inclination-Of-The-Night: Box 93
  - Lambda: The Carolina Gay and Lesbian Association Newsletter: Box 55
  - Lambda Book Report: Box 55
  - ΛΕΣΒΙΑ (Lambda Epsilon Sigma Beta Iota Alpha) International Women's News: Box 55
  - Lambda Rising News: Box 94
  - Lance: Box 55
  - Lavendar Woman: Box 55
  - Leap Leap: Shameless Hussy Review: Box 55
  - The Leaping Lesbian: Box 55
  - Left Curve: Box 5
  - Le'sbeinformed: Box 55
  - Lesbenfront: Box 78
  - Lesbenpresse: Box 77
  - Lesbia Magazine: Boxes 55, 56
  - Lesbian Connection: Boxes 20, 56-57, 77, 100
  - Lesbian Contradiction: Box 57, 77, 97
  - Lesbian Ethics: Box 19, 92
  - The Lesbian Feminist: Box 11
  - Lesbian Feminist Flyer: Box 57
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives Newsletter: Box 75, 84
  - Lesbian Inciter: Box 57
  - The Lesbian News: Boxes 4, 77, OS2
  - The Lesbian Review of Books: Box 57, 78
  - Lesbian Rights Project: Box 58
  - Lesbian Tide: Boxes 23, 58, 84, 101
  - Lesbian Visual Artists: Box 58
  - Lesbian Voices: Box 58
  - Lesbians on the Loose: Box 58
  - Letters from Harriet: Box 86
  - Leviahan: Box 85
  - Lezzie-Fair: Box 21
  - Lezzie Smut: Box 58
  - Liberation: Boxes 7, 58, 85
  - Libido: Box 58
  - Lilith: Box 59, 77
  - Listen Real Loud: Box 77
  - Lola Press: Box 81
  - Ludus: Box 59
  - Mach Quarterly: Box 73
  - Mademoiselle: Box 6
  - Madness Network News: Box 77
  - Maize: A Lesbian Country Magazine: Box 59
  - Majority Report: Boxes 18, 59, 85, 103
  - The Male Figure: Box 59, 78
  - Mama Bears News and Notes: Box 59
  - Mama Raga: Box 59
  - Manhattan Tribune: Box 85
  - Manifest Reader: Box 73
  - Manorama: Box 59
  - Manpower!: Box 59
  - Manual: Box 60
  - Maryland Commission for Women: Box 78
  - Masque: Revue des Homosexualites: Box 60
  - Matrix: Box 9
  - *Matrix: A Place of Our Own: Box 78
  - MAW: Box 18
  - Media Report to Women: Box 94, 101
  - Meeting Ground: Box 102
  - Metrosource: Box 75
  - Militant: Box 7
  - Mississippi Voice: Box 90
  - The Mole: Box 85
  - Mom's Apple Pie: Lesbian Mothers' National Defense Fund Newsletter: Box 60
  - The Monthly Extract: Box 89, 103
  - Mother: Box 41
  - Motive: Box 6, 85
  - Mountain Astrologer: Box 34
  - Moving Out: Box 36
  - Moxie: Box 60
  - Ms.: Boxes 18, 60, 61, 62, 85
  - Mujer/Fempress: Box 81
  - Muscleboy: Box 62
  - Mushroom Effect: Box 85
  - Musica: Box 85
  - Music Women: Box 85
  - Muthah: Box 4
  - My Trip Around the World: Box 62
  - NACLA's Latin America and Empire Report: Box 62
  - National Abortion Rights Action League Campus Newsletter: Box 62
  - National Anti-Pornography Civil Rights Organization: Box 78
  - National Center for Lesbian Rights Newsletter: Box 62
  - National Committee on Pay Equity: Box 77
  - National NOW Times: Boxes 13, 36, 37, 81, 96
  - National Times: Box 62
  - New Directions for News: Box 95
  - New Dawn for Women: Box 7
  - New Directions for Women: Boxes 5, 39, 95
  - New Moon: Box 20
  - The New Woman's Clinic, Inc.: Box 76
  - New York: Box 6
  - New York Blade: OS2
  - New York Feminist Tribune: Box 62
  - New York Pride Guide: Box 62
  - New York Blade: OS2
  - A Newsletter: Box 62
  - The Newsletter: Boxes 32, 38, 62
  - No Apologies: Box 73
  - No More Cages: Box 13
  - North Carolina Womenews: Box 77
  - North Carolinians United for ERA: Box 13
  - Northwest Passage: Box 41
  - Nosotras: Box 62
  - Le Nouvel Observateur: Box 62
  - NOW NOW NOW: Box 36
  - NOW: Hate Crimes Against Lesbians: Box 36
  - The Nuditarian: Box 86
  - NYQ: Box 75
  - Obeisance: Box 73
  - Of a Like Mind: Box 63
  - Off Our Backs: Boxes 5, 12, 14, 15, 16, 40, 63, 83, 85, 97, 102, 104
  - Older Women's League (San Francisco Chapter Newsletter): Box 63
  - The OLOC Reporter: Box 63
  - Older Women's League- Greater New York Chapter Newsletter: Box 77
  - On Our Backs: Boxes 63, 64, 75, 85, 103
  - On the Issues: Box 64, 83, 91, 94
  - One: Boxes 64, 65, 103
  - Onna erosu: Box 74
  - Onyx: Black Lesbian Newsletter: Box 65
  - Le Operaie della Casa: Box 65
  - Other Side: Box 8
  - Our Paper: Box 78
  - Out: Box 87
  - Out and About: Boxes 13, 65
  - Out in Black: Box 97
  - Outlook: Boxes 20, 65
  - Outweek: Box 75
  - Outrageous Women: Box 74
  - Pacific Coast Times: Box 77
  - Paid My Dues: Boxes 22, 89
  - Peacetalks: Box 65
  - The Pedestal: Box 41
  - Peking Review: Box 80
  - Pentimenta: Box 65
  - Physique Illustrated: Box 65
  - Plainswoman: Box 65
  - Plexus: Box 94, 103
  - Poder y Libertad: Box 65
  - Poets and Writers: Box 65
  - Pointblank Times: Boxes 11, 22
  - The Political Economy of Women: Box 78
  - Political Environments: Box 80
  - Pornography Awareness Newsletter: Box 77
  - The Power Exchange: Box 74
  - Power of Women: Box 65
  - Practicing Antiracism: Box 93
  - Primavera: Box 36
  - Prime Time: Boxes 11, 65
  - ProFemina: Box 79
  - Pucker Up: Box 65
  - Pursuit and Symposium: Box 77
  - Push: Boxes 36, 65
  - Q Notes: Boxes 21, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34
  - Quality of Life Digest: Box 77
  - Quadrille: Box 6
  - Quarterly Journal for the National Association of Mental Health: Box 77
  - Quest: Boxes 16, 65, 92
  - Quicksilver Times: Box 83, 86
  - QW: Box 75
  - Radical America: Box 83
  - The Radical Therapist: Box 85
  - RFD (Radical Fairies Digest): Box 65
  - Radical Historians: Box 80
  - The Radical Teacher: Box 40
  - The Radical Therapist: Box 77
  - Ramparts: Box 66
  - RAT Subterranean News: Boxes 7, 66
  - Red Rag: Box 80, 86
  - Redstockings: Box 5
  - Reveille, Box 97
  - Rockgrl: Box 85
  - Roger: Box 66
  - Room of One's Own: Box 36
  - Rundbrief Lesbenarchiv: Box 77
  - Sage Newsletter: Boxes 74, 75
  - SageWoman: Box 85
  - The Sandmutopia Guardian and Dungeon Journal: Box 74
  - Santa Cruz Women's Health Center Newsletter: Box 11
  - Sapphic Touch: Box 7
  - Sappho: Box 66
  - Sassy: Boxes 12, 66
  - Scarlet Women: Box 13
  - Second Wave: Boxes 18, 86, 103
  - Sessualita Procreazione Maternita Aborto: Box 67
  - Seven Days: Box 6
  - Sfinga: Box 78
  - She: Box 67
  - Shewolf's Directory of Wimmin's Lands: Box 89
  - A Shift in the Wind: Box 95
  - Sing Out!: Box 89
  - Sinister Wisdom: Boxes 1, 4, 10, 19, 67, 91
  - Sir Gee: Box 67
  - Siren: Box 40
  - Sister: Boxes 11, 67
  - Sisters: Box 3
  - Sisters Stand: Box 11
  - Socialist Review: Box 17
  - Society for Humane Abortion, Inc. Newsletter: Boxes 11, 67, 77
  - Sojourner: Boxes 18, 67, 85, 97
  - So's Your Old Lady: Boxes 23, 67
  - Sottosopra: Box 67
  - Source: Box 86
  - Southern Feminist: Box 97
  - Spare Rib: Boxes 20, 67, 89, 100-101
  - Spartan for Men: Box 67
  - Spectre: Boxes 18, 67
  - Spectrum: A Cooperative Newspaper for the Tallahassee Community: Box 97
  - Spinning Off: Box 12
  - The Spokeswoman: Box 18, 94
  - Storyletters: Box 67
  - Super Studs: Box 67
  - Symposium Newsletter: Box 78
  - Synapse: Box 36
  - Synergy: Box 87
  - Synthesis: Box 79
  - Task Force Report: Box 75
  - Taste of Latex: Box 74, 102
  - Tell-a-Woman: Box 11
  - Thesmophoria: Box 77
  - Third Wave: The Next Step in Philanthropy and Feminism: Box 67
  - This Month in Mississippi: Box 90
  - Time Canada: Box 7
  - Tooth and Nail: Box 67, 76
  - Transgender Tapestry: Box 98
  - Tres Femmes: Box 67
  - The Tribune: A Women and Development Quarterly: Box 95
  - Trigger: Box 67
  - Trim Studio Quarterly: Box 67
  - Triple Jeopardy: Box 80
  - Trivia: Box 2, 93
  - Troubadoura: Box 85
  - Under the Sign of Pices: Box 93
  - Unique: Box 67
  - Up from Under: Boxes 6, 67, 80, 86
  - Uranus: Box 68
  - Vector: Box 68
  - Velvet Fist: Box 40
  - Velvet Glove: Box 6
  - Velvet Park: Box 24
  - La Vie en Rose: Box 68
  - Vim: Box 68
  - Vindacacion Feminista: Box 68
  - Visibilities: Boxes 18, 68, 74
  - Vision: Box 5
  - Visions: Box 68
  - Voice of the Women's Liberation Movement: Boxes 40, 68
  - Voices: Box 89
  - We Ain't Got it Easy But...We Got It!: Box 13
  - A Web of Crones: Box 68
  - WHISPER: Box 78
  - WIA Newsletter: Box 11
  - Widening Circle: Box 93
  - WIN: Boxes 21, 68, 80
  - **Win Magazine: Box 77
  - Winnipeg Women's Liberation Newsletter: Box 76
  - The Wise Woman: Box 68
  - The Wishing Well: Box 68
  - Witchita NOW Times: Box 36
  - The Woman Activist: Boxes 38, 68
  - Woman Image: Box 97
  - Woman of Power: Boxes 10, 22, 68, 91
  - Woman Space: Box 5
  - Woman Spirit: Box 69
  - Woman to Woman: Box 101
  - Womanart: Box 6, 94
  - Womanbooks Review: Box 77
  - Womanist: A Newsletter for Afrocentric Feminist Researchers: Box 94
  - Womanist: Theory and Research: Box 94
  - Womanews: Boxes 13, 69
  - Woman's Art Journal: Box 16
  - Woman's Monthly: Box 98
  - Woman's World: Box 69
  - Women: A Journal of Liberation: Boxes 2, 3, 5, 10, 16, 69, 80, 86
  - Women Against Pornography Newsreport: Box 20, 78
  - Women and Art: Box 7, 16
  - Women and Film: Box 18
  - Women and Revolution: Box 13
  - The Women Artists Group News: Box 76
  - Women Artists News: Box 6
  - Women Energy: Box 70
  - Women in Struggle: Box 76
  - Women of Color News: Box 70
  - Women of Power: Box 100
  - Women of the Whole World: Box 5, 103
  - Women's Caucus for Art: Box 94
  - Women's Liberation: Box 7
  - Women's Liberation Newsletter: Box 80
  - Women's Resource and Action Center Newsletter: Box 94, 97
  - The Women's Page: Box 70
  - Women's Press: Box 35
  - Women's Review: Box 70
  - The Women's Review of Books: Boxes 70, 71
  - Women's Self-Defense: Box 101
  - Women's Struggle Notes: Box 71
  - Women's Times: A Newsletter of the Virginia Women's Studies Newsletter: Box 95
  - Women's World: Box 80
  - WomenSports: Box 40
  - Wommin Together: Box 13
  - Wonaac Newsletter: Box 77
  - Wordwrite: Box 78
  - Workers Struggle Supplement: Box 77
  - Workers World: Box 77
  - Working Woman: Box 7
  - The Wree-View: Boxes 11, 71
  - Writing on the Wall: Box 4
  - Yale Break: Box 80
  - Young Guys!: Box 71
  - The Young Physique: Box 71
  - Young Voices: Box 75
  - 10 Percent: Box 82
  - 75 Percent: Box 80
  - Notes from the Second Year: Box 103
  - People's Peace Treaty: Box 103
  - Resist: Box 103
  - Shrew: Box 104
  - Socialist Woman: Box 103
  - Harlot Herald: Box 103
  - Women Speaking: Box 103